Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Records SC0112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2002-221
  - Vacancy to Hire (Box 26)
  - Vice Provost/Computing (Box 26)
  - Visiting Scholars Reading Room (Box 26)
  - Web Classes (Box 26)
  - Wershaw, Mrs. Irving B. (Box 26)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 26)
  - White European Males (Box 26)
  - White House (Box 26)
  - White, Richard (Box 26)
  - Whitehead, Barry and Fritzi Beth (Box 26)
  - WEI T'O Associates Inc. (Box 26)
  - Wooliscroft, Michael (Box 26)
  - Work Analysis (Box 26)
  - Work Books (Box 26)
  - Work Restructuring (Box 26)
  - Workshops (Box 26)
  - Working Titles Assignment of/for selectors (Box 26)
  - Worker's Comp (Box 26)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd (Box 26)
  - WWW Conference (Box 26)
  - Yellow Pages (Box 26)
  - Zeitlin and Ver Brugge (Box 26)
  - Z39.50 Project (Box 26)
  - Yolla Bolly Press (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (Box 26)
  - User Studies (Box 26)
  - Yankee Book Peddler (Box 26)
  - Wilbur (Box 26)
- Policy and Procedure Manual, 1977-1982; Accession ARCH-2008-009
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2014-062
  - Stanford University Libraries BALLOTS software implementation records (2 VHS cassettes, photographic slides, and user manuals) (Box 1)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2014-072
  - Science Libraries reports, 1948-1993 (Box 1)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2015-027
  - Organization of American States Classification manual (Box 1)
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2015-152
  - Meyer/Falconer Collection Development, 1970s-1980s (Box 1)
- Harold A. Miller Library, records, 1984-1992; ARCH-2016-066
  - Miller Library-Fundraising Package, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dedication, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acknowledgment, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - August Dart Events, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Miller Library-Early Justifications, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miller Library-Final Checklist, 1989 Jun (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Miller Library-Fundraising-Misc., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Library Plaque, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Library Committee Meeting, 1985 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miller Library Fact Sheet, 1989 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Miller Library Costs, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Millers, Pru & Harold, Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mohr Visit/Packard, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miller-Archaeological, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Miller-Groundbreaking, 1988 Apr 26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Miller-Architect memos, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Miller Library-Floor Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Miller-Dart, Jane, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Miller Library-Move, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Miller-Prothro's, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miller-Pro Library letters, 1987 Nov (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miller Library-Architects, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miller-Drawings, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miller-SUL Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miller-Architect correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2016-131
  - Stanford University Libraries Policy and Procedure Manual, circa 1979 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-102
  - Media Walls, 1999 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-119
  - Author & Title Catalogs-J. Henry Meyer Library, 2 volume(s) (Box 1)
  - Subject Catalog: J. Henry Meyer Library, 1 volume(s) (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-120
  - Photographs of Library Events & Staff
    - David Weber's 25th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Library Staff/Events, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-139
  - Highwire Press
    - HP-Administrative Records, 1998-2002 (Box 1)
    - E-Journal User Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-207-143
  - Hopkins. History of Miller Library, 2017-143.01; 1 optical disc(s) (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-147
  - BALLOTS (Bibliographic Automation of Large Library Operations using a Time-sharing System) brochure, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Felt Banner (Box 1)
  - SPIRES-BALLOT film (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-149
  - miscellany Britannica: Beatrix Potter Sex & Class True Blue Jews in Parliament Seances The Blitz, 1998 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-247
  - John Bender, Warren R. Howell Award Program, 2016 May 6 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-281
  - Microtext collections in the social sciences and humanities: micro text guide, 1979; 7 binder(s) (Box 1)
  - IC Computer Clusters, 3 binder(s) (Box 2)
  - IC Newspaper Index, 1999; 1 binder(s) (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-015
  - Miscellaneous - Advisory Task Force on Collection Development, Department of French and Italian, 1983-1985 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-068
  - Stanford University Libraries Government Documents Dpeartment: International Governmental Organizations, 6th Edition, 1977 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-076
  - Records of Zachary M. Baker, Assistant University Librarian for Collection Development (Humanities) and Social Sciences Reinhard Family Curator of Judaica and Hebraica Collections (Box 1)
    - Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-280
      - Chem 130/132 Survey Results, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Socrates, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Affirmative Action, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Folio, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Internet, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - TIS-Technical Information Service, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Card Catalog, Closing of, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Swain Misc., 1977-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Pierre Van Rysselberghe Pubs @ Swain, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Filing Guidelines - Swain, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Filing rules, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2018-117
  - Ralph Libby Biographical Material, Obituary, 2012 (Box 1)